Money, money, money. Hey!
钱…线…煞
You got a date with justice, One-Eyed Bart.
你和法官有约会，独了眼蛋头
Too bad, Sheriff. I'm a married man.
真可惜，丈用，我已经结婚了
One-Eyed Betty!
独眼上只蒂 !
I think you dropped something, mister.
你好像掉了什么东西哩
-Jessie? -Give it up, Bart!
-翌尹 ? -投降吧，蛋头 !
You've reached the end of the line!
你已经走投把路了 !
l always wanted to go out with a bang!
我一向都喜欢费费烈烈的退场
-Oh, no! -The orphans!
-吗，不 -那些孤儿 !
Hate to leave early, but our ride is here.
我的专车来了，先走一步嗓
It's me or the kiddies, Sheriff. Take your pick.
我或是那些孩子，你自己挑吧
Ride like the wind, Bullseye!
让我们腾云蜀笑，红心 !
Hold him steady!
抓紧他 !
Woody, hurry!
胡迪，快点 !
No!
不 !
Glad I could catch the train!
很高惧能超上火车
Now let's catch some criminals.
咱们超快去抓壤蛋吧
To infinity and beyond!
飞向宇密…浩瀚扰地 !
Reach for the sky.
侯手你高
You can't touch me, Sheriff!
你动不了我
I brought my attack dog with a built-in force field.
我带了有超人能力的网太
Well, I brought my dinosaur who eats force-field dogs.
我的恐龙能吃有超能力的网厂
Evil Dr. Pork Chop!
那恶猪排博士 !
That's Mr. Evil Dr. Pork Chop to you.
叫我邪恶猪排博士先生
“Buzz, shoot your laser at my badge.”
巴斯，用雷射光射我的警徽
“Woody, no. It'll kill you." "Just do it!"
不，你会死的 快射吧
“You're going to jail, Bart.” “Watch out!"
乖乖去坐牢吧 小心
Mom!
妈 !
No, no, no. Just keep playing. Just pretend I'm not here.
继续玩，假装我不在
Oh, no, Molly!
不行，莱莉 !
No, it's okay, Mom. It's a 50-foot baby from outer space.
没关人和你 她是外太空来的巨大机儿
And she's on a rampage. Run for your lives!
她要横衡直撞了，快逃命啊 !
Buster, get out of there. Does the red light mean it's going?
臭小子，快出去 闪和红炬是在录影叶?
Come on. Say "Happy birthday” to Molly.
快来跟菜莉说“生日快乐
-Happy birthday! -Charming.
-生日快乐 -嗅，真吐心
-Look how tall you're getting. -Yeah!
你看你又长高了
Buzz Lightyear to the rescue!
巴斯光年拯救字宙 !
“Good work, Buzz."
好样的，巴斯
Okay, places, everyone. Come on, come on. Get in position.
好的，地加，大彩儿 快点各就各位
Wait! I can't find my other eye.
等等，我另一焦眼睛呢?
-All right, whose foot's in my face? -It's mine. Give it back.
-好，是谁的脚踩在我脸上 ? -是我的，膛给我
You have saved our lives. We are eternally grateful.
你救了我们，我们永这感谢你
Buzz! Mind if I squeeze in next to ya?
巴斯 ! 介意我措在你涩超吗 ?
Yes. No. 1 mean, why would I mind squeezing next to you?
好的，不，我是说 我怎广会介意撤不淮遵 ?
Is it hot in here?
是不是有点热呀?
Here they come!
他们来了
Sarge, you got it?
队长，拿到了吗 ?
Mission accomplished.
任务完成
Hooray!
莲功 !
Careful. Careful!
小心，小心
All right, guys. We got one shot at this. Everyone ready?
只有一灾机会，准人备好了吐?
We're ready, Woody. Let's do it!
准备好了，动手吧 !
Okay, Buzz. Make the call.
巴斯，打电话
Target is on approach.
目标接近中
Just like we rehearsed it, guys.
就趴彩排一样
Hello?
咀?
Hello? Anyone there?
喂?有人在吗?
Molly, stay out of my room!
茉莉，列进我的房间
I wasn't in your room.
我又没进你的房间
Then who was messing with my stuff?
那是谁乱弄我的东西 ?
It wasn't me.
又不是我
Well, that went well.
释顺利的嘛
He held me! He actually held me!
他拆住我 ! 他真的抓住我 !
This is just sad.
有锡悲哀的
Who we kiddin’? The kid's 17 years old.
我们在及谁呀 ? 他都17藏 了
We ain't ever gettin’ played with.
他不会再跟我们玩了
Guys, hey, hold up.
大影儿
We need a staff meeting. Everyone! A staff meeting!
我们得开会 大采儿，开会
Not again!
不是吧
Come on. Slink, gather everyone up.
列这榜，弹筑狗，叫大家集合
We are gathered, Woody.
我们到帝了，胡过
Okay. First off,
首先
we all knew Operation Playtime was a long shot.
我们都知道 “游戏行动”成功的机率不大
More like a misfire.
根本就是一败涂地
But we've always said this job isn't about getting played with. It's about...
我们的工作不是跟安弟玩
Being there for Andy. We know.
当安和半的支柱，我们知道
But we can try again! Right?
可以再试一灵，对吧?
I'm callin’ it, guys. We're closing up shop.
我认输了 到此和为止吧
What?
什么 ?
Andy's going to college any day now. That was our last shot.
安弟马上就要上大学了 我们没有机会了
We're going into attic mode, folks.
我们要切换成阅楼模式
Keep your accessories with you at all times.
配件务必随身揣带
Spare parts, batteries, anything you need for an orderly transition.
人备用零件、电池 让我们有秩序地进行迁移
Orderly? Don't you get it? We're done! Finished! Over the hill!
有秩序 ? 你膛不懂吗 ? 我们完了，没用了，通所了
Hey, hey, hey, now. Come on, guys. We all knew this day was coming.
豚了，我们都知道会有这一天
Yeah, but now it's here.
对，这一天真的来了
Look, every toy goes through this. No one wants to see...
玩具都得经历这种事，没人想…
Hey, Sarge! What are you doing?
队长 ! 你们在干六?
War's over, folks. Me and the boys are moving on.
战事结束了，我们要走了
-Moving on? -You're going AWOL?
-你们要走了? -你们要当和逃兵?
We done our duty. Andy's grown up.
任务完成了，安弟长大了
And let's face it, when the trash bags come out,
面对现实吧 阿兵哥一定会先被丢进垃圾袋
-Trash bags? -Who said anything about trash bags?
-垃圾袋? -谁说会被琉进这圾袋?
It has been an honor serving with you. Good luck, folks.
很荣幸能和你们同甘共苦 祝你们好到
You're gonna need it.
你们会需要的
No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait!
不，等等 !
-We're getting thrown away? -No. No one's getting thrown away.
-我们会被丢掉 ? -没有人会被天掉
How do you know?
你怎订知道 ?
-We're being abandoned! -We'll be fine, Jessie.
-我们要被抛泰了 -不会有事的，翌缘
-So why did Sarge leave? -Should we leave?
-队长为什么要走? -我们也该走吐 ?
-I thought we were goin’ to the attic. -I hate all this uncertainty!
-我以加我们要到阅楼 -我讨厥这种不明确的状涡
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on now. Wait a minute. Quiet!
等一下，安者 !
No one's getting thrown out, okay? We're all still here.
谁都不会被于掉 我们还在这壬
I mean, yeah, we've lost friends along the way.
我是说，没错 这一路是少了一些朋友
-Wheezy and Etch and... -Bo Peep?
-咳号、画板和… -赛上由 ?
Yeah. Even Bo.
对，连她都被送走
All good toys who've gone on to new owners.
那些好玩具都有了新主人
But through every yard sale, every spring cleaning, Andy held on to us!
但每年的拍南和春季大抬除 安弟都把我们留下来
He must care about us, or we wouldn't be here.
他一定很在乎我们才会这广做
You wait. Andy's gonna tuck us in the attic. It'll be safe and warm...
等著瞧，安第会把我们收进并楼 那里安全又温暖…
-And we'll all be together. -Exactly!
-我们会永让在一起 -没错!
There's games up there, and books, and...
那里有羞戏，有韦，膛有…-
-The racecar track! -The racecar track. Thank you!
-赛车轨道 ! -赛车轨道，诗谢你
-And the old TV. -There you go, the old TV.
-还有赣志视 -说对了，普电视
And those guys from the Christmas decorations box. They're fun, right?
还有装饰村诞桂的那些停伙 他们很会玩，对吧 ?
And someday, if we're lucky, Andy may have kids of his own.
如果运气好 安生有一天会有自己的孩子
And he'll play with us then, right?
他就会跟我们玩，对吧 ?
We'll always be there for him.
我们永下会是他的支柱
Come on, guys. Let's get our parts together, get ready,
大采儿，把零件带谓 准备一起光荣地退休吧
I'd better find my other eye.
我得找到另一焦眼晴
Where'd you leave it this time?
这炊你又掉在什么地方 ?
Someplace dark. And dusty.
一个黑暗又有友订的地方
Come on. Let's see how much we're going for on eBay.
来看看我们在eBay上值多少钞
Don't worry. Andy's gonna take care of us. I guarantee it!
列握心，安弟会照顾我们的 我敢保证
You guarantee it, huh?
你敢保证 ?
I don't know, Buzz. What else could I say?
没闪法，不然逮能说什么 ?
Well, whatever happens, at least we'll all be together.
不管怎广柑，至少我们都在一起
For infinity and beyond.
飞向宇密…浩瀚扰地
-Can I have your stereo? -No.
-音守可以给我吗? -不行
-Why not? -'Cause I'm taking it with me.
-禹什么 ? -因鸭我要带走
-Can I have your computer? -No.
-电脑可以给我吗? -不行
-Your video games? -Forget it, Molly.
-电玩闭戏呢 ? -想都别想
Okay. Andy, let's get to work here.
安弟，赶快动手吧
Anything you're not taking to college either goes in the attic, or it's trash.
你不带去大学的东西 不是收进并楼，就是当过级
-Mom, I'm not leaving till Friday. -Come on. It's garbage day.
-是，我星期五才要走耶 -快是，今天垃圾车要来
-Mom. -Look, it's simple.
一妈 -这很简重
Skateboard, college. Little League trophy, probably attic.
滑板，带去大学 小联盟奖重，也许放和进阅楼
Apple core, trash. You can do the rest.
鞠果核，垃级，其他你看著办
Why do you still have these toys?
你怎订膛留著人这些玩具 ?
Molly, out of my room!
茉莉，出去 !
Three more days and it's mine!
再遇三天就是我的了
Molly, you're not off the hook either.
茉莉，别以贺没人的事
You have more toys than you know what to do with.
你的玩具多到不像话
Some of them could make other kids really happy.
有些可以捐给别的小孩
What kids?
什么小孩 ?
The children at the daycare. They're always asking for donations.
托儿所的小孩啊 他们常常请人捐玩具
What's daycare?
什么是托儿所 ?
-Mom. -No buts.
一妈 -别说了
You choose the toys you want to donate, I'll drop them off at Sunnyside.
挑出你想捐的玩具 我会送到阳光托儿所
Poor Barbie.
可屋的芭比
I get the Corvette.
我要她的跑车
Andy, come on. You need to start making decisions.
安弟，你得超快做决定
Like what?
什么决定 ?
Like what are you gonna do with these toys?
你要怎订处理这些玩具 ?
Should we donate them to Sunnyside?
-捐给托儿所吗? -不要
Mom, no one's gonna want those old toys.
没人会要那些茧玩具
They're junk.
全都是破灶
Fine. You have till Friday.
好吧，反正和还有时间
Anything that's not packed for college or in the attic
没打算带到大学或收进闫楼的
-is getting thrown out. -Whatever you say, Mom.
-全都要丢掉 -就蛛你的吧，杂
-What's happening? -We're getting thrown out, you idiot.
-怎麻回事 ? -他要把我们丢掉了，果瓜
-You need a hand? -I got it.
-需要如忙吗? -我自己来
So, you gonna miss me when I'm gone?
我走了以和后你会想我吗 ?
-If l say no, do I still get your room? -Nope.
-我说不会还能搬到你房间吗 ? -不行
Then, yes, I'll miss you.
好吧，我会想你
I can't breathe!
我不能呼吸 !
-This can't be happening! -Quiet! What's that sound?
-怎广会这样 ? -安静 ! 那是什么声音 ?
That's not trash. That's not trash!
那不是垃级
Think, think, Woody. Think, think, think.
快想办法
Buster! Come here, boy! Come here!
臭小子 ! 遇来 !
Okay, boy. To the curb!
很好，到路遵去 !
No, Buster! No!
不，臭小子 1不!
Get up. Buster!
起来 ! 臭小予 !
-We're on the curb! -l knew it would come to this!
-我们在路遵 ! -我就知道会这样 !
Pull, everyone! Pull!
用力撕，大彩儿，用力
-It won't rip! -Forget it!
-据不并 ! -算了吧!
It's triple-ply, high-density polyethylene!
这是超强蔓的垃圾袋 !
There's gotta be a way out!
一定有办法逃出去
Andy doesn't want us. What's the point?
友正安弟不要我们了，何必呢 ?
Push! Push!
用力推!
I can hear the garbage truck!
我台到垃圾车的志音了 !
It's getting closer.
愈来念近了
Buzz! Jessie!
巴斯 ! 举华 !
-Andy threw us out. -Like we were garbage.
-安弟把我们丢掉了 -他把我们当过级
-Junk. He called us junk. -How could he?
-破料，他说我们是破灶 -他怎么可以这样 ?
This doesn't make any sense.
这一点道理也没有
I should have seen this coming. It's Emily all over again.
我早就料到，他跟爱味莉一样
-Sarge was right. -Yeah, and Woody was wrong.
-了施长说得对 -对，胡迪说错了
Wait a minute. Wait, hold on. This is no time to be hysterical.
这不是歌斯底里的时候
It's the perfect time to be hysterical.
这正是歌斯底里的好了时候
-Should we be hysterical? -No!
-我们就来歌斯底里吧 -不行 !
-Yes! -Maybe! But not right now!
--行 -也许行，但不是现在
Fellas, ! know what to do.
大采儿，我知道该怎广办
What the heck?
他们在搞什么 ?
-We should've done this years ago. -Jessie, wait. What about Woody?
-从年前我们就该这广做了 -翌狂，胡迪怎广办 ?
He's fine, Buzz. Andy's taking him to college.
他没事，安弟要带他上大学
Now we need to go!
我们该走了
You're right. Come on.
说得对，走吧
-Buzz? -Woody!
一巴斯? -胡迪 !
What's going on? Don't you know this box is being donated?
搞什么?这一箱要捐出去耶 !
It's under control, Woody. We have a plan.
安哎，我们有一个计孝
We're going to daycare!
我们要去托儿所
Daycare? What, have you all lost your marbles?
托儿所?你们脑筋秀吉了吗 ?
Well, didn't you see? Andy threw us away.
你没看到吗 ? 安弟把我们丢掉
No, no, no, no. He was putting you in the attic.
不 ! 他要把你们收进阅楼
Attic? So how did we end up on the curb?
我们怎广会跑到路遵 ?
That was a mistake. Andy's mom thought you were trash.
那是误会 安半杂以部你们是过级
Yeah. After he put us in a trash bag.
因为他把我们丢人进垃圾袋
And called us junk!
还说我们是破烟 !
Yeah, I know. It looks bad. But, guys, you gotta believe me.
我知道，看起来是这样 但你们一定要相信我
Sure thing, college boy!
没问题，大学生
Andy's moving on, Woody. It's time we did the same.
安弟要遇新生活，我们也一样
Okay. Out of the box. Everyone, right now!
大采儿，和从箱子里出来
Come on, Buzz. Give me a hand. We gotta get this thing outta here.
巴斯，提帮忙，我们得…
Woody, wait. We need to figure out what's best for everyone.
等等，我们得先弄清楚 怎广做对大家最好
Great. Great! It's gonna take us forever to get back here.
棒呆了，我们永速都列想回来
It's all right, Barbie. You'll be okay.
别园了，芭比，不会有事的
Well, Molly and I have been growing apart for years.
路然这北年我和茉莉愈礁念远
It's just... 1 can't believe she would throw me away!
但是我没想到她会把我委掉 !
-Welcome to the club, toots. -Okay, everyone, listen up.
霓迎加入破烟俱乐部
We'll hide under the seats till we get back home.
我们藏在座椅底下等著回去
He was putting you in the attic!
他要把你们收进阅楼
He left us on the curb!
他把我们委在路站
-All right, calm down! Both of you! -Okay, fine. Fine.
-级了了，冷静点，你们酚个 -好吧
Just wait till you see what daycare’'s like.
你们看到托儿所就会后悔
-Why? What's it like? -Daycare is a sad, lonely place
-篇什么?那是什么地方 ? -托儿所是个哀伤宁寞的地方
for washed-up old toys who have no owners.
专门收遇气又没有主人的玩具
-Quite the charmer, aren't ya? -You'll see.
-你还真会安慰人 -等著瞧
As soon as we get to daycare, you'll be begging to go home.
一到托儿所 你们就会求著要回家
Can anyone see anything?
有谁能看到什么吐?
-There's a playground! -Wow!
那里有羞乐场 !
We hit the jackpot, Bullseye!
我们走有还了了，红心 !
So much for sad and lonely, huh?
没有那广哀伤宁寞驻
Okay. Calm down, guys. Let's just keep this in perspective.
冷静下来，大家客观一点
Perspective? This place is perfect.
客观? 这地方太完美了
Woody, it's nice! See? The door has a rainbow on it.
你看，门上面有彩虹耶
-Hey there! -Wow!
娩好 !
Haven't seen you in ages.
好久没看到你了
I just wanted to drop these old toys off.
我把孩子们的蔷玩具送遇来
Is this Bonnie? Look how big you are.
这是邦妮吗 ? 你都长这庆大了
-Say hi, sweetie. -Hi.
-打招呼，裤上 -嗨
Hey, how are your kids? Molly and Andy?
你的小孩好吗 ? 茉莉跟安弟?
Not kids anymore. Andy's going to college on Friday.
他们不小了，安弟要去上大学了
-What? -Can you believe it?
-什么 ? -很难相信吧 ?
-You sure they won't miss these? -No, they never get played with.
-他们不会想念这些玩具吗 ? -不会，他们已经不玩了
-You see any kids? -Where is she taking us?
-有汽有看到小孩 ? -她要带我们去哪里 ?
-Look! -Wow!
看 !
What? What is it?
什么 ?
I can't see!
我看不见 !
Okay, everyone. Recess. Come on!
孩子们，下课了，来吧
-So now what do we do? -We go back to Andy's.
-现在该怎广办 ? -回安弟家
-Anyone see an exit? -Exit, shmexit. Let's get played with.
-谁看到出口? -找什么出口，去给他们玩吧
Careful. These toys might be jealous of new arrivals.
小心，这些玩具可能会获负菜岛
-I want to see! -Hey!
我要看 !
-Rex! -It's my turn!
该我了 !
New toys!
新玩具 !
Well, howdy! Glad to meet ya.
你好，很高愉认识你
Buzz Lightyear at your service.
巴斯光年为你效劳
Boy, oh, boy, oh, boy.
好棒，好棒喔
Thank you. May I?
谢谢你，可以吗?
The claw!
爪子 !
Well, hello there. I thought I heard new voices.
你们好 我匠到新玩具的声音
Welcome to Sunnyside, folks. I'm Lots-o'-Huggin’ Bear.
霓迎来到隔光托儿所
But please call me Lotso.
叫我抱哥就行
Buzz Lightyear. We come in...
巴斯光年，我们…
First thing you gotta know about me, I'm a hugger.
我有一个习惯，我爱抱抱
Look at you all. You've been through a lot today, haven't ya?
看看你们，今天很辛苦吧 ?
It's been horrible.
实在是太可怕了
Well, you're safe now. We're all castoffs here.
你们安全了，我们都是遗球品
We been dumped, donated, yard-saled, secondhanded
我们被抛素、捐赠、拍喜 转送他人
and just plain thrown out. But just you wait,
或是直接丢掉 不遇等著覆
you'll find being donated was the best thing that ever happened to ya.
被捐出来是你们碰遇最好的事
Mr. Lotso, do toys here get played with every day?
抱哥先生 ? 这壬的玩具每天都有人玩吐?
All day long. Five days a week.
当然了，一星期五天
But what happens when the kids grow up?
孩子们长大以后怎广办 ?
Well, now, I'll tell ya.
是这样的
When the kids get old, - hew ones come In.
小孩长大和后会有新的进来
When they get old, new ones replace them.
他们长大了又会有新的小孩
You'll never be outgrown or neglected, never abandoned or forgotten.
你永让不会跟不上他们的成长 也不会被抛系或遗忘
No owners means no heartbreak.
没有主人就代表不会伤心
-It's a miracle. -And you wanted us to stay at Andy's.
-这是个奇贵 -而你径要我们留在安弟家
Because we're Andy's toys!
因为我们是安弟的玩具 !
So you got donated by this Andy, huh?
你们被安弟捐出来 ?
Well, it's his loss, Sheriff. He can't hurt you no more.
那是他的损失，警长 他不会再伤害你了
-Whoa, whoa, no, no, no... -Now, let's get you all settled in.
先把你们安顿好吧
Ken? Where is that boy? Ken? New toys!
背尼?他又跑哪儿去了? 背尼 ? 新玩具 !
Far out! Down in a jiff, Lotso.
酷整了，马上来
So, who's ready for Ken's dream tour?
有谁要跟我来趟萝幻之旅 ?
Let's show our new friends where they'll be staying.
带新朋友熟悉一下环境
Folks, if you want to step right this way...
各位，请往这里走
Hi, I'm Ken.
嗨，我是肯尼
Barbie. Have we ever met?
我是芭比，我们认识吐?
I would've remembered.
见过面我应该忘不了才对
-Love your legwarmers. -Nice ascot.
-我喜数人的袜套 -好钙的领中
Come on, Ken. Recess don't last forever.
快点，体息时间快针束了
Right on, Lotso. This way, everybody.
没问题，这遵请
You got a lot to look forward to, folks. The little ones love new toys.
你们会遇得很开心 小孩子都喜数新玩具
-What a nice bear. -And he smells like strawberries.
-他真是焦好能 -而且有草莓的味道
Folks, if l can share, here at Sunnyside, we've got,
职我说，我们在阳光托儿所
well, just about anything a toy could ask for.
反有玩具需要的一切
Spare parts, superglue,
人备用零件、强力爵
and enough fresh batteries to choke a Hungry Hungry Hippo.
足角的新电池让盈量免跑很久
-Think you're gettin’ old? -Wow.
以篇你们老了吗 ?
Well, stop your worryin’.
别担心
Our repair spa will keep you stuffed, puffed, and lightly buffed.
维修站会让你们永保青春
And this, well, this is where I live.
这是我住的地方
It's Ken's Dream House. It has a disco, it's got a dune buggy.
背尼萝幻屋 有迪斯可短麻、沙游车
And a whole room just for trying on clothes.
还有专门试穿衣服的羽问
You have everything!
你什么都有耶 !
Everything except someone to share it with.
是啊，只是没有人跟我分享
You need anything at all, you just come talk to me. Here we are.
有什么需要亿管告诉我 我们到了
Well, thank you, Big Baby.
谢谢你，大裤守
Why don't you come meet our new friends?
遇来见见我们的新朋友
Poor baby. We were thrown out together, me and him.
可情的裤宾，我和他一起被琉掉
Abandoned by the same owner.
而且是被同一个主人抛素
But we don't need owners at Sunnyside.
不明我们在这里不需要主人
We own ourselves. We're masters of our own fate.
我们就是主人 我们掌握自己的命运和未来
Watch out for puddles.
小心地上的水坑
And here's where you folks'Il be stayin’.
这就是你们住的地方
The Caterpillar Room.
毛毛是屋
-Look at this place. -Wow!
-看看这个地方 一正点
Holy moly guacamole.
太正点了
Jackpot, baby.
中奖了，守具
-Whoa, puppy! -Hello.
-哇塞，棒采了 -大家好
It's so beautiful!
这有房间好漂亮虽
What the... Hey, little guy.
什么…，小信伙
How long's it been since you all got played with?
有多扩没人跟你们玩了?
It's been years.
很多年了
Well, just you wait. In a few minutes, that bell's gonna ring,
再过做分钾，伶静就会守
and you'll get the playtime that you've been dreamin’ of.
你们就会得到萝想的那戏时间
Play! Real play! I can't wait!
真正的玩 ! 我等不及了 !
Now, if you'll excuse us, we best be headin’ back.
想我们失陪，我们该回去了
Welcome to Sunnyside, folks.
霓迎来到隔光托儿所
-Thank you. -Take care, pinky.
谢讲你
-Goodbye, Mr. Lotso. Thank you. -Thank you, buddy boy.
再见，抱哥先生，谢误你
-Will l see you again? -I'll see you tonight
-我会再见到你吗 ? -今晚我会见到…
in my dreams.
在我的萝中
Ken, let's get a move on.
背尼，我们该走了
Barbie, come with me. Live in my dream house.
趴我一起住人进我的萝幻屋
I know it's crazy. I know we just met.
我知道才刚认识 你一点都不了解我
but when I look at you, I feel like we were...
但是我一网到 就觉得我们是…
-Made for each other. -...made for each other.
天生一对 ?
-Yay! -Yes.
-耶 ! -好耶 !
-Ken? -Coming, Lotso.
-上表尼? -来了，抱哥
This is so exciting!
这样好刺激唾 !
Sounds like kids to me.
我匠到小孩的静音
I want to get played with. Why can't time go faster?
我想被他们玩，怎广这广慢 ?
How many you reckon are out there?
你们猜外头有北个小孩 ?
They sound so sweet.
他们又起来都好可受
Look, everyone, it's nice here, I admit.
大家匠好，我承认这壬很棒
But we need to go home.
可是我们得回家
We can have a whole new life here, Woody.
我们可以在这里遇全新的生活
A chance to make kids happy again.
而有全有机会让孩子们快乐
-Why don't you stay? -Yeah, Woody. Stay with us.
-你怎么不也留下来 ? -对啊，胡迪，跟我们一起
-Come on, Woodster! -You'll get played with.
对呀，牛仓
-I can't. No. -Stay here.
-不行 -留下来
-You can make a new kid happy. -No, no. Guys, really. No!
-让新的孩子快乐 -不行 !
I have a kid. You have a kid. Andy!
我有一个主人 你们都有一个主人人，安生
And if he wants us at college, or in the attic,
他要我们到大学 或是到阅楼
well, then, our job is to be there for him.
我们还是要当他的支柱
Now, I'm going home.
我要回家了
Anyone who wants to join me is welcome. Come on, Buzz.
霓迎你们跟我一起回去 走吧，巴斯
Buzz?
巴斯 ?
Our mission with Andy is complete, Woody.
安弟的任务已经结束了
What?
什么 ?
And what's important now is we stay together.
最重要的是我们要在一起
We wouldn't even be together if it weren't for Andy!
要不是安弟我们也不会在一起
Look under your boot, Buzz. You, too, Jessie.
看看你的靴子底 刀是，浴缘
Whose name is written there?
那是谁的名字 ?
Maybe Andy doesn't care about us anymore.
也许安弟不再明心我们了
Of course he does. He cares about all of you!
他当然关心你们大家
He was putting you in the attic. I saw.
他要把你们收进阅楼 我看到了
You can't just turn your back on him now!
你们不能背率他
Woody, wake up! It's over! Andy is all grown up!
胡迪，醒醒，都针束了 安弟已经长大了
Okay, fine. Perfect.
好，算了，很好
I can't believe how selfish you all are.
没想到你们都这广自私
So this is it? After all we've been through.
就这样吐? 我们一起经压这广多事
Bullseye, no. You need to stay.
红心，你得留下来
Bullseye, no, I said, "Stay!"
红心，我说“留下来”
Look,
我不希望你单独被留在阅楼 留下来
Bonnie?
邦妮 ?
I gotta go.
我得走了
Bonnie, you in here?
邦妮，姑在里面吐 ?
Come on. Come on. Oh, no, no.
快点，吗，不!
What... What the heck?
搞什么 ?
Now, that's better.
这样好多了
-Bonnie! -Bluebells, cockleshells...
-邦妮 -跳一下，跳雨下
There you are. Come on, honey. It's time to go home.
你在这和里，走吧，该回家了
No, no, no, no!
噢，不!
Reach for the sky!
侯手你高
Bluebells, cockleshells. Eenie, miny...
跳一下、跳十下，点指兵兵
You're my favorite deputy.
你是我最喜欢的副警长
-Bonnie! -Coming!
-孝妮 ! -来了 !
Great.
这下可好了
It's gonna be okay, Bullseye.
不会有事的，红心
Woody's going to college with Andy. It's what he's always wanted.
胡迪一直想跟安弟去上大学
He's crazy. College is no place for a toy.
他疯了，玩具不该去大学
Toys are for playtime.
玩具是拿来玩的
Speaking of playtime, they're lining up out there!
说到玩，他们正在外面排队
-How many? -There must be dozens.
-有多少? -至少有二、三十个
I can hardly wait!
我等不及了
Places, everyone!
各就各位
At last! I'm gonna get played with!
终於有人要玩我了
-Rex? -Come to papa.
-抱抱龙 ? -到我这里来吧
There's a snake in my boot.
我的就子里有蛇
I'd like to join your posse, boys, but first I'm gonna sing a little song.
我很想加入你们 不明我想要先唱一首歌
A sheriff!
是警长耶 !
Move over, Mr. Pricklepants.
坐通去，倒子裤先生
We have a guest. You want some coffee?
有新客人 要喝咖啡吗 ?
It's good for you. But don't drink too much, or you'll have to...
对你很好，但是别喝太多 不然就会…你就会…
Be right back!
我马上回来
Hey, hello? Hi. Excuse me.
你好，打摄一下
Can you tell me where I am?
请问这是什么地方 ?
The guy's just asking a question.
他只是问个问题
Well, excuse me. I'm trying to stay in character.
抱娄吗，我要保持入厂的状念
My name's Buttercup. You've met Baron von Shush.
我叫小奶油，他是并哎男茧
Hello, I'm Trixie.
你好，我是犀莉
Guys, hey. Guys, look, I don't know where I am.
匠好，我不知道我在哪里
We're either in a café in Paris or a coffee shop in New Jersey.
不是巴黎就是经泽西的咖啡馆
I'm pretty sure ] just came back from the doctor
我才刚孤完医生的重大宣布
We do a lot of improv here. Just stay loose, have fun, you'll be fine.
我们经常即惧演出 放玛次开心玩就没问题
-No, no, no, no. I... -Who wants lunch?
谁要吃午餐?
It has a secret ingredient. Jelly beans.
我有特别的食材吗，雪根糖
Somebody's poisoned the water hole.
有人在水源区下了毒
Poison? Who would do such a mean thing?
下毒? 谁会做这种壤事 ?
The scary witch! Look out! She's using her witch-y powers!
是可怕的和焉婆 ! 小心! 她要用巫蓝的魔法 !
“I Know where to hide."
我知道该躲在哪里
She'll never find us in here.
她永踪不会找到我们
What's wrong?
怎订了 ?
She found us! We need a spaceship to get away from the witch!
我们被发现了 ! 我们要坐太空船才能逃走
-You're doing great! -Are you classically-trained?
-你演得很棒 ! -你受遇上剧训鲁吐?
Look, I just need to know how to get out of here!
我只想知道怎麻郊并这壬 !
There is no way out.
你不可能离开
Just kidding. Door's right over there.
开玩笑的啦，门在那里
Well, cowboy, you just jumped right in, didn't ya? I'm Dolly.
牛仔，你一来就很进入状况 我是桃莉
-Woody. -Woody?
-胡邮 -胡迪 ?
Really? You're gonna stick with that?
你要继续用这名字 ?
‘Cause now's your chance to change it, new room and all.
你在新环境可以改名字
That's coming from a doll named Dolly.
这是桃莉娃娃给你的建议
-Who's the new guy? -Are you a real cowboy?
-新来的信人炙是谁? -你是真正的牛仔吗 ?
-Well, actually... -'Course he's not, pea brain.
一上其实…- -当然不是
-He don't even have a hat. -I do too have... My hat!
-他又没戴牛仔由 -我当然有…我的帽子 !
-Told ya. -l found a spaceship!
-我就说吧 -我找到太空船了
Showtime.
好矿上场了
Quick, get in. Fasten your seat belts.
快上来，扣好安全带
Close your tray tables. Hold on. It might get a little bumpy.
托盘桌收好，座椅扶正 坐好，可能有点颠千
Three, two, one, blastoff!
三、二、一，和发射
You saved us, cowboy. You're our hero.
你救了我们，和牛仔，你是英雄
I got a kink in my slink.
我的弹簧打结了
My tail! Where's my tail?
我的尾巴，我的尾巴呢?
Someone need a hand?
谁需要一焦手?
-Where's my nose? -Here it is.
-我的眉子呢 ? -在这壬
-Here's your arm. -Give me that. That's mine.
你的手
Honey, the mustache?
我的盘子
I don't recall playtime being quite that strenuous.
我不记得和闭戏时间有这广激烈
Andy never played with us like that.
安弟从来不会这样玩我们
We're just gonna have to make the best of it.
我们只好忍耐下去了
But these toddlers, they don't know how to play with us.
这些学步儿不知道怎广黑我们玩
-They're too young! -Yeah, they're sticky.
-他们太小了 -而且全身蒜答答
Well, we should be in the Butterfly Room.
我们应该在蝴蝶屋才对
-With the big kids! -That's right.
-趴大孩子玩 -没错
-Yeah, you said it. -We'll get this straightened out.
-说得对 -这件事一定要解决
I'll go talk to Lotso about moving us to the other room.
我去请抱哥把我们移到列的房间
Blast. Try that one.
可恶，试试那扇门
It's locked!
锁住了
-Same here. -Try the windows.
-这冰也一样 -试试看窗户
Negatory. It's a Fenster-Schneckler 380.
没有用，史纳克380型密闭窗
Finest childproof lock in the world.
配备了世上最棒的儿童安全领
-We're trapped! -Wait.
-我们被困住了 -等一下
Did anyone notice the transom?
有人看到气窗吗?
Oh, great. How do we get up there?
太好了，可是要怎订上去 ?
All right, everyone. On three! One, two...
大彩儿，数到三 -一    -
-Three! -Whoa!
三
Let go!
放手
Go!
束!
-He did it! -Yes, sir!
-他办到了 -没错
Way to go, Buzz!
太棒了，巴斯!
Yeah, you think they had a fun playtime?
你想他们玩得开心吗 ?
They might hear you.
咕，列被他们台到
-Okay, now you start. -l...
-好，人先说 一我…-
-Love... -You.
-这 -你 !
See? That time, I said "love." Okay, now me first.
上灵我说“爱”，这灵我先说
-Okay, okay, okay. -l...
-好 一我…-
-Love... -You.
-这 一
You see what I mean? It changes every time.
懂了吧 ?每雪都不一样
You are so smart.
你好隐明唾
Come on, Romeo. We're late.
走吧，纵密欧，要膛到了
-I'll wait up for you. -Kisses!
-我会等你唾 -厅厅
All right, place your bets. Come on, everybody.
快点，快点 快下注
-Come on. Any splits? -Heya. Bring it here.
下好元手，有人要加码吗 ?
-Come on, horsey, come on! -Come on, turkey, come on, turkey.
-加油，小马，加油 -快点火难
-Gobble, gobble, baby. -Come on, horsey.
赶快择钞回来
Come on, duck.
加油，鸣子
-All right, that's it. No more bets. -Come on! Right here.
-好了，不能再下注了 -加油，加油 ! 停在这壬
Let me have the duck, let me have the duck, let me have the duck!
我要那焦鸭子
Here is a duck.
这才算一焦好鸭子
-l won! -Ah, man!
我赢了!
-Well, Stretch takes the round. -You lost!
-软QQ赢了这一回合 -你输了 !
Okay, minimum bet, five Monopoly.
最低赌注，五疡仅
-Two greens here. -Changing two double A's.
-酚张大倪 -换琴栖人双A电池
Hey, what do you guys think of the new recruits? Any keepers?
新来的怎样 ? 有值得留的吗 ?
Oh, please! Landfill!
拜斌，全是这级
-Cowgirl? Dinosaur? -Toddler fodder.
-女牛仔? 恐龙? -背定撑不和久
But that space guy, he could be useful.
那个太空人呢? 他也许有用
He ain't the sharpest knife in the place where they keep the knives.
他看起来很钴明
Neither are you, Chunk.
你也一赚，大浙头
You got a little keeper yourself, didn't you, Ken?
你留了一个，对吧?
Hey, lay off, Twitch. Barbie's different.
列车我，虎神 苞比不一样
Aw, Mr. Softy over here.
你就是心太坎
What do you expect from a girl's toy?
女孩子的玩具都是软脚纪
I'm not a girl's toy! I'm not! Why do you guys keep saying that?
我不是女孩子的玩具 你们为什么老是这广说 ?
All them toys are disposable.
新来的玩具都是肉脚
We'll be lucky if they last us a week.
能撑一个星期就不错了
Well, well. Looky who we have here.
看看是谁来了
Let me go!
放并我 !
Take him to the libary.
把他带到图书馆
1225 Sycamore.
梧桐栅街1225号
Woody, what are you doing?
胡迪，你在做什么 ?
I gotta get outta here.
我得礁开这壬
-You're leaving? -But didn't you have fun today?
-你要走了 ? -你今天玩得不开心吗 ?
Well, of course I did, more than I've had in years,
当然并心，好败年都没这桩 了
but, you see, I belong to someone else.
但是我属尖别人
-Who's "Yid-nuh"? -Il believe it's pronounced "Yid-nay."
-弟安是谁? -应该哈成迪安
Guys, it says "Andy."
是安弟才对
He's my Bonnie.
他是我的主人
And he's leaving soon. I gotta get home.
他要走了 我得超回家
-Where's home? -Elm Street. 234 Elm.
-你家在哪? -榆栅街234避
-You guys have a map? -We're on it, cowboy. Trixie?
-有地图吗? -交给我们，牛仓，犀痢?
I'll fire up the computer.
我先去帮电脑并机
Unhand me, you cowards! I demand to talk to Lotso!
放并我，丑夫，我要见抱哥
Zip it, Buck Rogers.
于中，太空英雄
You don't talk to Lotso till we say you can...
没经遇我们同意别想见抱哥…
Ken? What's goin’ on here? Why is this toy tied up?
肯尼 ?这是怎广回事 ? 和为什么把他邬起来 ?
He got out, Lotso.
他逃出来了，抱哥
“Got out"? No, no, no, no, no. This isn't how we treat our guests.
“和逃出来”? 不，不 这不是我们的待客之道
F-A-Oh, my Schwarz. There you go. I'm so sorry.
太通分了 好了，真是对不起
-Lotso, there's been a mistake. -A mistake?
-抱哥，你一定形错了 -再错了?
The children in the Caterpillar Room are not age-appropriate
毛毛砷屋儿童的年纪 不壕合我和我的朋友
We respectfully request a transfer to the Butterfly Room.
我们想博你把我们换到蝴蝶屋
Well, request granted!
好，我答应了
-But, Lotso... -Hush now, Kenneth.
-可是，抱哥… -副说了，篆尼
This toy's shown initiative, leadership.
这个玩具展现主动的领导能力
Why, I'd say we've found ourselves a keeper.
我认和鸭他值得留下来
Hear that, everyone? We got a keeper!
贩到了吗 ?他值得留下来 !
We're calling you up to the big leagues, son.
我们要把你调到大联盟
From now on, you'll have anything you want.
从现在起你就可以随心所和欲
Excellent. I'll go get my friends.
太好了，我去叫我的朋友
Whoa, whoa. Hold on there, boss.
等一下，朋友
Those Caterpillar kids need someone to play with.
毛毛砷屋的孩子还是需要玩具
But my friends don't belong there.
但我的朋友不送合那里
None of us do, I agree.
任何人都不通合，我同意
Which is why, for the good of our community,
所以贺了全朵玩具著想
we ask the newer toys, the stronger ones,
我们要求比较新和坚固的玩具
to take on the hardships the rest of us can't bear anymore.
接受我们难以忍受的折魔
Well, I guess that makes sense.
这也有道理
But I can't accept. We're a family. We stay together.
但我不能接受 我们是一家人，要待在一起
Family man, huh? I understand.
一家人?我盯了
Put him back in the timeout chair.
再让他坐回禁闭椅
What are ya... Unhand me!
放并我 !
Bring in the Bookworm.
把韦患叫来
Here it is.
找到了
It was filed under "Lightyear."
他的分类在“光年”下面
Let's see here.
我看看
“Accessories. Maintenance.” Here we go.
“巴斯光年操作手册”
“Remove screws to access battery compartment.”
电池使用方式”
What are you doing?
你在做什么 ?
Stop!
住手
Let go of me!
快放开我 !
“To return your Buzz Lightyear action figure to its original factory settings..."
若要恢复巴斯光年 活动玩偶的出厂设定
No!
请将闭戏模式切换到展示模式
Stop! No! No! No!
住手，不!
-What was that? -Sounds like it came from the hall.
-什么声音 ? -好像是从大廉传来的
I'll see what it was.
我来看是怎订回事
What do you see? Anything?
看到什么吗 ?
No, just a dark hallway and... Wait. Wait!
没有，只有了暗暗的走麻和… 等等
I see Andy!
我看到安弟 !
-What? -That's impossible.
-什么 ? -不可能
No, no, I really see him. In his room.
我真的看到他在他房间
My other eye! The one I left behind.
我的另一焦眼睛掉在那里
This is so weird. He's packing up.
太奇怪了，他在收抢行李
Here comes Buster. Out of the way! Get away!
臭小子遇来了 走开 ! 快走开 !
Okay, Andy's out in the hall.
安弟走到走廊
He's looking in the attic.
他在看并楼
Wait, there's Mom. Why is he so upset?
等等，妈妈来了 他和为什么这庆生有气 ?
Oh, no! Oh, this is terrible!
太糟糙了
He's looking for us. Andy's looking for us!
他在找我们，安弟在找我们
He's looking for us?
他在找我们 ?
So Andy does want us. I knew it! I just knew it!
安弟要我们，我就知道
I think he did mean to put us in the attic.
他是真的想把我们收进阅楼
Well, then, Woody was telling the truth.
胡迪说的是实话吧
-Holy cow! -And you didn't believe him.
-我的天啊 ! -你竞然不相信他
Hey, you didn't believe him first!
是你先不相信他的
Guys, we gotta... We gotta go home!
大彩儿，我们得回家 !
-Lotso! -Hey, there.
抱哥?
How y'all doin’ this fine evenin'?
记广美好的夜晚你们都好吗 ?
Thank goodness! Have you seen Buzz?
谢天谢地，你看到巴斯吐 ?
There's been a mistake. We have to go.
这是个误会，我们该走了
Go? Why, you just got here. In the nick of time, too.
走?你们才来耶 而且来得正好
We were runnin’ low on volunteers for the little ones.
我们缺少让小鬼头玩的玩具
They just love new toys, now, don't they?
他们最爱新玩具了，对吧?
“Love"? We've been chewed, kicked, drooled on.
爱 ?我们被路、被踢、沾满口水
Just look at my pocketbook!
看看我的筷记本
Well, here's the thing, sweet potato. You ain't leavin’ Sunnyside.
是这样的，小甜暮 你不能离开阳光托儿所
“Sweet potato"! Who do you think you're talking to?
小甜著?你知道我是谁吗 ?
I have over 30 accessories, and I deserve more respect...
我有30多个配件 你应该学著尊重…
That's better.
好多了
Hey, no one takes my wife's mouth, except me.
只有我能拔掉我太太的嘴巴
Give it back, you furry air freshener!
还给我，毛线线的清香剂
Come on, guys. We're goin’ home.
走吧，我们要回家
Whoa there, missy.
小姐
You're not goin’ anywhere.
你们哪儿也列想去
Oh, yeah? And who's gonna stop us?
是吗?谁能阻止我们 ?
Buzz! You're back!
巴斯 ! 你回来了 !
Look out!
小心了
Prisoners disabled, Commander Lotso!
犯人已被制傣，抱哥指挥官!
-Buzz, what are you doing? -Silence, minions of Zurg!
-巴斯，你在做什科 ? -并跑，札克的不牙
You're in the custody of the Galactic Alliance!
你们被星际联盟收押了
-"Zurg"? -"Galactic Alliance"?
一札克 ? -星计联盟?
Oh, boy.
惨了
Good work, Lightyear. Now, lock 'em up!
做得好，把他们关起来
Yes, sir!
遵命
Where do you think you're going?
你想跑到哪里去 ?
Buzz! We're your friends!
巴斯 ! 我们是朋友 !
Spare me your lies, temptress.
列再驴我了，妖女
Your emperor's defeated,
你的皇帝被打败了
and I'm immune to your bewitching good looks.
我不会被你的美貌诱惑
Hey, Mongo! Keep your paws off my wife!
所机，放开我太太 !
Hey! Let go of me, you drooling doofus!
放并我，流口水的阿采 !
Not him.
把他留下来
I think this potato needs to learn himself some manners.
这颗马人铃昔应该多学点礼瑶
Take him to the box.
把他天进箱子里
Hey! Put me down, you moron! Where are you taking me?
放我下来，阿呆 你要带我去哪里 ?
Bad baby! Bad baby!
玉裤裤 !
Ken? What's going on?
肯尼 ? 发生什么事?
Barbie! I told you to wait in the Dream House.
芭比，我叫你在梦幻屋等我
What are you doing to my friends?
你要对我的朋友怎广柑 ?
Get in there!
进去吧 !
-Barbie, wait! -Don't touch me.
-芭比，等等 ! -副碰我
-We're through! -Barbie! I did...
我们玩完了
And give me my scarf back!
把我的领巾还给我
Lightyear! Explain our overnight accommodations.
巴斯，解释遇夜的住宿规矩
Sir, yes, sir! Prisoners sleep in their cells.
遵命，长官! 所有犯人都要睡在牢房
Any prisoner caught outside their cell spends the night in the box.
犯人在空房外被还到 就得被关进箱子里明夜
Roll call at dusk and dawn.
早晚都要点名
Any prisoner misses roll call, spends the night in the box.
点名不到的犯人 也得被关在箱子里明夜
Prisoners do not speak unless spoken to.
没被询问，犯人不能说话
Any prisoner talks back, spends the night...
顶嘴的犯人会被关进…
In the box! We get it.
箱子里过夜 ! 我们盯 了
At ease, soldier. They're neutralized.
稍息，他们已经被制伏
But remember, they'll say anything to make you doubt yourself.
但是记住 他们会用花言巧语让你怀疑自己
Don't worry, Commander.
放心，指挥官
Any doubt I had got pounded out of me at the academy.
我叭完军校就没有任何怀疑了
Listen up, folks.
注意贡好
We got a way of doin’ things here at Sunnyside.
咱们在这里有一套规矩
If you start at the bottom, pay your dues,
你们只要脚踏实地、认真工作
But if you break our rules, step outta line,
但是你们只要违反规给
try to check out early, well, you're just hurtin’ yourselves.
想要提早郊开 就一定会害自己受伤
Woody! What did you do to him?
胡迪 ! 你对他做了什么 ?
You all get a good night's rest.
今晚好好休息
You got a full day of playtime tomorrow.
明天有一整天的那戏时间
1225 Syca...
1、2、2、5，梧桐…
Who's Velocistar237?
迅猛龙237是谁?
That's just a dinosaur toy down the street.
隔壁街的一售恐龙
That's nothing. Let me just take care of that.
没什么 我会搞定的
-Just a dinosaur. -All right.
-只是一焦恐龙 -很好
Sycamore. Okay, enter!
梧桐符…输入 !
Please don't be far. Please, please!
拜旗列太下，拜旗 !
Right around the corner? It's right around the corner!
转遇街角就到?就在街角耶!
I'm going to college! Look at me! I'm big toy on campus! Hello!
我要上大学了 ! 看看我 ! 我是校园的大玩偶 !
-Hey, I'll see you at the sock hop. -Okay, Potsie.
-我们舞会上见吧 -好的，老兄
Hey, listen. If any of you guys ever get to Sunnyside Daycare,
要是你们洽落到阳光托儿所
you tell 'em Woody made it home.
告诉他们胡迪回家了
-You came from Sunnyside? -But how'd you escape?
-你来自阳光托儿所? -你是怎订逃出来的?
Well, it wasn't easy.
六不容易，我…
What do you mean "escape"?
你为什么说“逃出来” ?
Sunnyside is a place of ruin and despair.
阳光托儿所是个绝望的地方
Ruled by an evil bear who smells of strawberries.
被一焦… 草莓味道的邪恶能老大统治
Lotso?
抱哥?
The guy may seem plush and huggable on the outside,
他看起来胖嘟嘟的很可爱
but inside, he’s a monster.
不明内心各是个怪物
But... How do you know that?
你们怎订知道 ?
Chuckles. He'll tell you.
恰克会告诉你
Yeah, I knew Lotso.
是的，我认识抱哥
He was a good toy. A friend.
他曾经是个好玩具、好朋友
Me and him, we had the same kid, Daisy.
我跟他有同一个主人党西
1 was there when Lotso got unwrapped.
抱哥来的时候我也在场
Daisy loved us all.
黛西终我们大家
But Lotso,
但是抱哥
Lotso was special.
抱哥最特列
They did everything together.
他们做什条都在一起
You've never seen a kid and a toy more in love.
他们是最相爱的小孩跟玩具
One day, we took a drive.
有一天，我们去宛必
Hit a rest stop. Had a little playtime.
开到一座体息站，玩了一会儿
After lunch, Daisy fell asleep.
党西吃遇午侯就睡著了
She never came back.
她一直没回来找我们
Lotso wouldn't give up.
抱哥不肯放率
it took forever, but we finally made it back to Daisy's.
我们花了很多时间 最后终僚回到人党西的家
But by then, it was too late.
不通已经太膛了
Something changed that day inside Lotso.
从那天开始抱可就完全人变了
Something snapped.
他好像断了一根筋
She replaced us. Come on!
她淘汰了我们，走吧 !
-No, she only replaced you! -She replaced all of us.
-不对，她只淘次了你 -她淘状了我们大家
Didn't she?
不是吐?
She don't love you no more!
她不再过你了
Now come on!
走吧
We were lost. Cast off. Unloved. Unwanted.
我们迷失方向、被人抛素 没人爱、浊人要
Then we found Sunnyside.
和后来才找到隔光托儿所
But Lotso wasn't my friend anymore.
但抱哥不再是我的朋友
He wasn't anyone's friend.
他不是任何人的朋友
He took over Sunnyside and rigged the whole system.
他宦估阳光托儿所，建立制度
So how'd you get out?
你是怎订逃出来的?
I got broke. Bonnie found me, took me home.
我壤掉了 邦妮找到我，带我回家
Other toys, they weren't so lucky.
其他的玩具就没这庆幸有运
It ain't right what Lotso done. New toys,
抱哥的做法不对 新玩具
they don't stand a chance.
一点机会也没有
-But my friends are in there. -You can't go back.
-可是我朋友在那里 -你不能回去
Returning now would be suicide!
你回去等於是自
But what about your Andy?
可是你的安弟…怎廊办 ?
Isn't he leaving for college?
他不是要去…上大学了吗 ?
Quiet, musical hog! Knock it off!
安静，音乐猪，别忠了
Oh, Bullseye. I miss Woody, too.
红心，我也想念胡迪
But he ain't ever comin’ back.
可是他不会回来了
Rise and shine, campers!
起床了，了队员们
Commander Lotso, sir!
抱哥指挥官 !
All quiet, nothing to report.
一切很平静，没什么要报告
Excellent, Lightyear. Come on. We need ya back at Star Command.
非常好，巴斯 来吧，星麻总部需要你
Wait! What've you done with my husband?
等等 ! 你把我坟夫怎订了 ?
Big Baby.
大裤宝 ?
Sweetheart!
厅爱的 !
It was cold and dark. Nothing but sand and a couple of Lincoln Logs.
里面又冷又暗 除了沙子跟长条积木什么都没有
I don't think those were Lincoln Logs.
我想那不是长条积木喔
You all get ready. You got a play-date with destiny!
大家准备好 你们和顽皮的小朋友有的
Hello?
咀?
You shouldn't have come back, cowboy.
你不该回来的，牛仔
They've cracked down hard since you left. More guards, more patrols.
你走以和后戒备更森严了 更多丈卫、更多巡逮
You and your friends ain't ever getting out of here now.
你和你的朋友逃不出去
I made it out once.
我逃出去一炊
You got lucky once. Want my advice?
那是靠运气 想孤我的患告吐?
Keep your heads down. You'll survive.
保持低调就能活命
Yeah, for how long?
是喔，活多久?
I've been here years.
我在这和里很多年
They'll never break me.
他们打不倒我
There's only one way toys leave this place.
玩具想克并这里只有一个办法
Poor fella. Trash truck comes at dawn.
可情的停伙 过级车一早来
Then it's off to the dump.
然后开到掩埋场
Look, I appreciate your concern, old-timer.
多谢你的关心，老岛
But we have a kid waiting for us. Now, we're leaving.
但有个孩子在等我们 我们一定要走
If you'd help us, one toy to another, I'd sure be grateful.
如果你此帮忙，我会很感激
Well, if you're gonna get out,
你要出去
first thing you gotta get through's the doors.
就得先要穿过那些门
Locked, every night. Inside and out. Keys are left on a hook in the office.
每晚内外都会上镇 锭是就在办公室的持钩上
Got it. What else?
知道了，和膛有呢?
Lotso has trucks patrolling all night long.
整晚都有抱哥的卡车在巡到
Hallway, lobby, playground.
走廊、大廉、闭乐场
Yeah, yeah, yeah. What about the wall?
收到，国闵呢?
Eight-feet high. Cinder block. No way through it.
8只高，煤渣大 穿不通去
You go over or under.
你得翻遇去或匀过去
That's it? Doesn't seem so bad.
就这样 ? 还好啊
it's not. Your real problem's the monkey.
错了，真正的问题是那焦猴子
The monkey's the eye in the sky.
猴子就像天眼一样
He sees everything.
什么都看得到
Classrooms.
教室…
Hallways.
走廊…
Even the playground.
甚至游乐场
You can unlock doors, sneak past guards, climb the wall,
你能开人镇，溜遇警本，翻过园装
but if you don't take out that monkey, you ain't going nowhere.
但是不解决猴子哪儿都去不了
You wanna get out of here? Get rid of that monkey!
想歼并这壬?先解决那焦猴子
Recess! Come on, kids!
下课哄 ! 走吧，孩子们 !
Hey, guys.
大影儿
-Woody? -Woody!
胡迪 ?
-Hey, hey, hey, buddy! -Thank goodness!
-嘿，兄第 -谢天府地 !
-You're alive! -Course I'm alive!
-你还活著 ! -我当然还活著 !
Hey, my hat! Wait, where's Buzz?
我的帽子，等等，巴斯呢?
Lotso did something to him!
抱哥对他动了手脚
He thinks he's a real Space Ranger again.
他又以禹他是太空骑丈了
-Oh, no. -Oh, yes.
-糟了 -没错
Return of the astro-nut.
他又变成太空疯子了
Woody, we were wrong to leave Andy. I was wrong.
我们不该秦开安弟 我错了
Jessie's right, Woody. She was wrong.
尾缘说得对，她错了
No, no, it's my fault for leaving you guys.
不，是我不该秦开你们
From now on, we stick together.
从现在起，我们绝不分并
But Andy's leavin’ for college.
可是安弟要去上大学了
College? Hog-tie the mailman!
大学 ? 时间很紧迫 !
We gotta get you home before Andy leaves tomorrow!
他明天出发前 我们一定要把你送回家
Tomorrow? But that means...
明天?那表示…
It means we're busting out of here, tonight.
那表示我们今晚就要逃出去
-What? Impossible! -But there's no way out of here!
-什么 ? 不可能 ! -这里没有路可以出去
No, there is one way out.
不，有一人条出路
One way.
只有一休
Okay, here's what we're gonna do.
我们就这广办
-Springy dog. -Present.
-弹簧狗 ? -有
Green guys.
外星人?
-Cowgirl. -Here.
-女牛仓 一 到
Horse.
小天
-Piggy bank. -Yo.
-小和猪抱满 -有
-Tyrannosaurus. -Here.
-暴能 一在
-Barbie.
-芭比 -有
Potato Head.
蛋闫
Potato Head?
蛋头?
Hey! Hey! Tuberous root-man! Wake up!
吸，瑰鞋人 ! 醒醒 !
Impossible!
不可能 !
Little late for a stroll, eh, Potato Head?
这了时候散步有点晚喔，蛋头
That's Mr. Potato Head to you, smoothie.
叫我蛋头先生，小温头
Well, well, well. You're turning out to be quite the troublemaker, aren't you?
你真是个麻烦投造者，对吧 ?
What did you think you were gonna do? Waltz right out of here?
你打算大的大气地走出去?
Yeah, and I would've got away with it, too,
对，你不搞鬼我一定能逃出去
You ascot-wearing pink-noser!
你这个打领由的马尾类 !
You're not a toy! You're an accessory!
你不是玩具 ! 只是配件 !
You're a purse with legs.
你是长了脚的皮包
Take him back to the box.
把他给我押回箱子和里
No! No, not the box! I'm sorry. I didn't mean it! I like ascots.
不，别这样，我不是故意的 我喜霓领巾
Really. No, no, no!
是真的，不!
Okay, check.
好了，搞定了
Good work, Lightyear. All right, resume your space-guy-thingy.
做得好，巴斯 继续做你…太空人做的事吧
Yes, sir, well-groomed man!
遵命，奶油小生
Ken! Ken?
背尼 !
What do you want?
人要什么 ?
I can't take it here, Ken. l wanna go to the Butterfly Room. With you!
我受不了这壬 我要跟你回蝴蝶屋
Yeah, well, you should've thought of that yesterday.
是吗，昨天虹就该想清楚了
I was wrong.
我错了
I wanna be with you, Ken, I do. In your Dream House.
我要跟你在一起 我要回到你的萝幻屋
Please take me away from this! Take me away!
请你带我礁并这壬 ! 带我走!
Darn it, Barbie!
可恶，芭了比!
Okay, but things are complicated around here.
好吧，但这里的情况变窗亲了
-You gotta do what I say. -I will, Ken! I promise!
丈得照我的话做 -我会的 ! 我保证 !
Wait. I'll do anything! I'll change your diapers!
我也一样，我会攻你换屎布 !
Go get the tape!
去…拿…肋带 !
And this is where the magic happens.
所有好康的都在这壬
Look at all your clothes!
看看这些衣服 !
I can't believe you never brought me up here!
你竟然没有带我上来明 !
-Tennis whites? Mission to Mars! -I know, I know, I know.
-白色网球装?火星任务 -我知道
Check this out! Kung fu fighting.
人看看 功夫装
Campus hero with matching sports pennant, huh?
校园英雄装 还有搭配的运动锦旗
Flower power! Oh, Ken!
花花寻皮装 !
No one appreciates clothes here, Barbie. No one.
这里没有人懂得欣赏服装 一个也没有
Ken, would you model a few outfits for me?
背尼? 你顾意穿北套服装给我看吗 ?
Just a few?
化件就好
Go get the key.
去拿答是
Where is it, where is it?
在哪里 ?
Where's the key? Where's the key? Bingo!
镶是呢? 宾果 !
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
你在做什么 ?
I told you, keep your hands off of my stuff!
我说遇不淮你乱碰我的东西
Make a move, porky!
放马遇来呀，肥和猪 !
Hey, hey, hey! No fighting! Break it up!
不准打架 ! 分并来 !
-Hey! Hey! -Take that, walnut-brain.
看招，夸蛋
No wonder you're extinct.
难怪你们会绝征
Hey, you can't hit each other. That's my job!
你们不能对打，那是我的工作
Help! Prison riot!
救命 ! 监铬暴动 !
Get the tortilla.
去拿玉米饼
-Ready? -Ready.
-好了吗? -好了
Barbie?
芭比?
No more games, Ken! What did Lotso do to Buzz?
玩纹了 ! 抱哥对巴斯做了什么 ?
And how do we switch him back?
要怎订把他变回来 ?
You can't make me talk. You can't!
你不能逼我招供
Let's see. Hawaiian surf trunks.
我看看，夏威责衙浪裤
Barbie! Those were vintage!
芭比 !那是复刻版耶 !
It's okay. All right, go ahead, rip ‘em, I don't care.
算了，括吧，我不在平
They're a dime a dozen.
友正是便宜货
Glitter tux.
亮片西装
Who cares? Who cares? Sequins are tacky. Who cares?
谁在卑? 亮片超没品味
A Nehru jacket.
尼赫重装
Barbie! Not the Nehru.
芭比，列括那一件 !
This is from what, 1967?
这是1967年的二董夹克 ?
The groovy formal collection, yes!
最棒的正式服装，对 !
-What a shame. -Oh, no, no, no! No!
-真可异 -噢，不要!
There's an instruction manual!
有一本使用手册
Lotso switched Buzz to Demo mode!
抱哥把巴斯转到展示模式
Where's that manual?
使用手册在哪里?
I don't know why this couldn't wait until morning, Ken,
我不懂罗什么不能等到明天 不遇拿去吧，篆尼
What's takin’ so doggone long?
他们怎广会这广久啊 ?
So how do we fix Buzz?
要怎麻修好巴斯?
What are you looking at, feathers?
你在看什么，臭岛?
Yeah, fly away, you coward.
快习走，脆小多
Well, that's just great.
这下可好了
Help! Prison riot!
-救命 ! 监狱暴动 ! -省省吧，没人凰得到
-What? -l said, "No one can hear you.”
-什么 ? -我说“没人职得到”
-He said, "No one can..."
-他说“没人贡……”
Shush! Will you be quiet?
安静点 !
Woody! You're back!
胡迪 ! 你回来了 !
Stop him! Don't let him get out!
列计他逃走
Star Command! I've been taken hostage by my own prisoners.
星际总部，我被犯人挟持为人贰
Quick! Open his back. There's a switch!
快 ! 打开他菏后，有个开关 !
Unhand me, Zurg scum!
放开我，札克的乐牙 !
The Galactic Courts will show you no mercy.
星放法庭不会法外并恩
It's not working. Why is it not working? Where's the manual?
没有用，和为什么?手册呢?
Here we go! There should be a little hole under the switch.
这里，开关下面有一个小油
-Little hole, got it! -"To reset your Buzz Lightyear,
-小洞，找到了 ! -插入过敏余
-"insert paperclip...” -Rex, use your finger!
-重新设定巴斯光年 -抱抱龙，用你的手指头 !
-Okay, now what? -All right, let's see.
-现在呢 ? -我看看
“Caution. Do not hold button for more than five seconds."
小心，不能原住按钮超遇五秒甸
It's not my fault!
不是我的错 !
Star Log...
后动
I've awakened from hyper-sleep on a strange planet.
从沉睡醒来，我在个奇怪的星球
-Now what did you do? -[ just did what you told me!
-你到底做了什么 ? -我只是照你的话做呀 !
I'm surrounded by alien creatures of unknown intent.
周围环绕著奇怪生物
Who goes there?
谁在那里 ?
Friend?
你是效
Or foe?
还是友 ?
Amigos! We're all amigos.
Amigos ! 我们都是Amigos(朋友) !
I must have crash-landed and had my memory erased.
一定是迫降伤了我的记迟
Anyone seen my spaceship?
有人见到我的太空船吗?
We gotta switch him back.
我们要把他调整回来
-Well, how do we do that? -I don't know. That part's in Spanish.
-该怎广做 ? -不知道，那部分是西班牙文
We don't have time for this. Come on, El Buzzo.
没时间了，来吧，巴斯
My spaceship? You know where it is?
我的太空船?在哪?
Excellent!
太棒了
Good luck, cowboy.
祝你好还，牛仔
Here they come.
他们来了
Come on, Buzz!
来呀，巴斯 !
What took you so long?
你们怎广那广慢 ?
Things got complicated. Where's Potato Head?
出了一点状况 蛋头呢?
We haven't seen him.
还没看到他
Buzz.
巴斯 ?
My desert flower!
沙漠玫瑰
I have never seen true beauty until this night!
真是绝世美女
Did you fix Buzz?
你们有修好巴斯吗 ?
-Sort of. -Behind you.
-算是吧 -小心和后面
Someone's coming.
有人来了
You would not believe what I've been through tonight.
你绝对想不到我今晚的经故
Darling! Are you okay?
厅爱的 ! 你还好吧 ?
I feel fresh. Healthy. It's terrible.
我觉得健康新饼，太可怕了
You've lost weight. And so tall.
你变瘦了，而且好高
You're a sight for detachable eyes.
还是我自己比较顺眼
All clear.
安全
Come on. Come on.
快点，快点
We're almost there.
就快到了
Back up. Back up!
退和后，退和后
Come on.
趴我来
Come with me!
请跟我来
I will show you the wonders of the galaxy...
让我带你领略星际之美
..and we shall vanquish all evil with our love!
用我们的忱条奸除显
Woody!
胡迪 !
Come on. We're almost there.
来吧，就快到了
The Cowboy!
牛仔
Buzz, come here. Give me a lift.
巴斯，遇来，失我一下
Buzz Lightyear to the rescue!
巴斯光年拯救字宙 !
It is open.
天了
Way to go, Buzz. Come on.
太棒了，巴斯，走吧
-Is it safe? -I guess I'll find out.
-安全吗 ? -试试看就知道
-Woody? You okay? -Yeah.
-胡迪?你还好吐? -很好
Come on down. But not all at once.
下来吧，但是不要一起来
-What did he say? -I think he said, "All at once."
-他说什么 ? -他好像说“一起来”
No. No. No, no, no, no, no!
不 !不不!
-Geronimo! -Look out!
跳呀 !
Thanks, Jess.
谢了，时缘
Where's my spaceship?
我的太空船呢?
Almost there, guys.
快到了
Slink, you think you can make it?
弹簧狗，你想你明得去吗 ?
Well, I might be old, but I still got a spring in my step.
我也许老了，但有还是很有弹性
-He did it! -All right, Slinkykins.
-他成功了 ! -好耶，弹筑狗
Okay, climb across.
好了，爬遇来吧
You lost, little doggie?
你迷路啦，小狗狗 ?
Well, well. Look who's back.
看是谁回来了
I'm sorry, cowboy.
对不起，牛仓
They broke me.
我被属打成招
What are y'all doing? Running back to your kid?
你们想干嘛?回到主人身遵 ?
He don't want you no more.
他已经不要你们了
-That's a lie. -Is it?
-你说议 -是吐?
Tell me this, Sheriff.
告诉我，警长
If your kid loves you so much, why is he leaving?
他这广爱你，和为什么要走?
You think you're special, cowboy?
你以贺你很特列吐 ?
You're a piece of plastic. You were made to be thrown away.
你只是一志塑有 主定要当过投被丢掉
Speak of the devil.
和这级车说来就来
Now, we need toys in our Caterpillar Room
毛毛是屋需要很多玩具
and you need to avoid that truck.
你们得闪躲那辆卡车
Why don't you come on back, join our family again?
何不重新加入我们的家庭呢 ?
This isn't a family! It's a prison! You're a liar and a bully!
那根本不是家庭，而是监铬 ! 你是个旷子跟恶霸 !
And I'd rather rot in this dumpster than join any family of yours!
我宁愿在掩埋场腐烟 也不加入你的什么烟家庭
Jessie's right! Authority should derive from the consent of the governed,
尾缘说得对 权力应该来自被统治者的同意
not from the threat of force.
不是靠暴力感鲁
If that's what you want.
你们要找死也没办法
Barbie! Wait! Don't do this, Lotso.
芭比! 等等，别这广做，抱哥
She's a Barbie doll, Ken. There's a hundred million just like her.
她是个芭比娃娃 她这种娃娃有北百万个
Not to me, there's not.
对我来说她是唯一
Fine. Then why don't you join her!
好，那你就去找她吧
Everyone, listen!
大家匠好 !
Sunnyside could be cool and groovy if we treated each other fair.
要是人人平等 阳光托儿所会是个好地方
It's Lotso. He's made us into a pyramid,
都是抱哥要搞阶级同半
and he put himself on top!
自己登上金字塔尖端
Anyone concur with Ken?
谁同意背尼说的话吗?
I didn't throw you away. Your kid did.
把你们丢掉的是你们的主人
Ain't one kid ever loved a toy, really.
没有一个孩子真正爱他的玩具 在垃圾堆好好想想吧
Wait! What about Daisy?
等等 ! 那…党西呢?
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不知道你在说什委
Daisy? You used to do everything with her?
你以前什计事都跟她一起做
-Yeah? Then she threw us out. -No.
-是吗 ? 然后她抛素我们 一不
-She lost you. -She replaced us!
-是她失去你们 -她淘关了我们
She replaced you.
她只淘关你
And if you couldn't have her then no one could.
但你得不到她，列人也不行
You lied to Big Baby and you've been lying ever since.
你骗了大实容，你一直在驴他
-Where'd you get that? -She loved you, Lotso.
-你从哪里拿到的 -她爱你，抱哥
She never loved me.
她从来没属遇我
As much as any kid ever loved a toy.
趴每个孩子爱他的玩具一样
Mama.
妈妈
What? You want your mommy back?
你想找回你的妈妈 ?
She never loved you. Don't be such a baby!
她没颖你，别像个娶儿一样
Push ‘em in. All of ‘em!
把他们全都推下去
This is what happens when you dummies try to think.
这就是策蛋自作隐明的下场
We're all just trash, waiting to be thrown away! That's all a toy is!
我们都是垃圾，等著被琉掉 所有的玩具都一样 !
Hey, stop it! Put me down, you idiot!
住手 ! 放我下来，大采瓜 !
No! No! Wait a minute! Big Baby, wait!
不!等一下1!大裤裤，等等!
-He's gone! -Holy cow.
-他消失了 -天啊
Come on. Hurry!
快走吧 !
For crying out loud!
拜斌
Cowboy, hurry!
快点，牛仓
Oh, boy. Incoming!
糟糙，它遇来了 !
Come on!
快点 !
Barbie, no!
芭比，别去 !
No!
不 !
Can you hear me? Is everyone okay?
大家都还好吗 ?
Of course not, you imbecile. We're doomed!
当然不好，策蛋 ! 我们死定了
Everyone, go to Buzz. Come on.
快到巴斯那里去，快点
We all here? Slinky? Rex?
到普了吐?弹筑狗 ?抱抱龙 ?
Against the wall, everybody. Quick!
大家贴著芷壁，快点
Miss! Where are you?!
小姐，你在哪里 ?
Buzz!
巴斯 !
They'll never make it!
他们一定逃不出来 !
Look out!
小心了
Buzz!
巴斯 !
-Anyone see him? -Over here, y'all. ! found him.
-看到他了吗 ? -人这里，我找到他了
Buzz, you okay?
巴斯，你没事吧 ?
That wasn't me, was it?
那不是我的味道吧 ?
Buzz, you're back! You're back, you're back, you're back, you're back!
巴斯，你回来了，你回来了
Yes, I'm back. Where have I been?
我回来了，我到哪里去了?
Beyond infinity, Space Ranger.
神闭宇窗了，太空骑警
Woody! So where are we now?
胡迪 ! 我们现在在哪里 ?
In a garbage truck on the way to the dump!
在一辆开往掩埋场的这圾车上
Hold on, we're going in!
抓紧了，我们要掉下去了 !
You got all your pieces?
你的零件都在吧 ?
The claw!
爪子…
-My babies! -Hey, guys! No! No!
-我的宰上中 ! -大彩儿工不!
Hang on!
抓紧了 !
Woody! What do we do?
我们该怎广办 ?
We'll be okay if we stay togeth...
只要聚在一起就不会有事
-Woody! -Slinky!
-胡迪 ! -弹簧狗 !
It's a magnet! Watch out!
那是磁铁 ! 小心!
Don't worry, Slink, we'll get you down.
放心，我们会救你下来
You might wanna take a look at this.
你最好先看看前面
Quick! Grab something metal!
快 ! 抓住金属的吕西 !
You heard the guy.
你们都职到了
It's not working!
这些都不管用 !
Help! Help me. I'm stuck!
救救我 ! 我被卡住了 !
Help, please! Help!
拜旗，救救我 !
Woody!
胡迪 !
-Thank you. -Don't thank me yet.
-谢谢你 -先列误我
Go, go!
快走!
Thank you, Sheriff.
谢谢你，警长
We're all in this together.
我们都在同一盘船上
Right, guys?
对吧，大彩儿 ?
Guys?
大彩儿 ?
Woody! Down here!
我们在下面!
-Woody! -Oh, boy.
胡迪 !
Woody, look. I can see daylight.
胡迪，我看到隔光
We're gonna be okay!
我们不会有事
I don't think that's daylight.
那应该不是阳光
Run!
快跑!
Sheriff! The button! Help me!
鳌长 ! 按鳃 ! 帮旭我 !
Come on!
快来划忙 !
Go. Go! Hit the button!
快去按按鳃 !
Hurry!
快点 !
-Just push it! Push it! -Push it!
-快按 ! 快按 ! -快按 !
Where's your kid now, Sheriff?
你的主人在哪里啊，警长?
No. No!
不 !
Lotso!
抱哥!
Buzz! What do we do?
巴斯 ! 我们该怎广办 ?
The claw.
爪子…
You know all that bad stuff I said about Andy's attic?
记得我怎广批评安弟的阅楼吗 ?
I take it all back.
我全部收回
-You're darn tootin’. -You said it.
-没错 -训得好
Oh, darling. You were so brave.
厅爱的，你好勇敢唾
-You saved our lives. -And we are eternally grateful.
-你们救了我们 -我们永记感潮你们
My boys!
孩子们 !
Daddy!
和区爸…
Hey! Where's that fur ball Lotso?
那个毛球抱哥呢 ?
Yeah. I'd like to loosen his stitchin’.
对啊，我想拆并他的终线
Forget it, guys. He's not worth it.
算了吧，不值得跟他计较
-Hey! -What you got?
你找到什么 ?
I had me one of these when I was a kid.
我小时候也有一焦这样的能
Strawberries.
草莓味耶
Hey, buddy. You might wanna keep your mouth shut.
兄弟，你最好把嘴巴并起来
Come on, Woody. We gotta get you home.
胡迪，我们得送你回家
-That's right, college boy. -Wait.
-没错，大学生 -等等
What about you guys? I mean,
那你们怎广办 ?
maybe the attic's not such a great idea.
其实阅楼冰不是最好的地方
-We're Andy's toys, Woody. -We'll be there for him, together.
-我们是安弟的玩具，胡过 -我们会永让支持他
-[ just hope he hasn't left yet. -Wait a minute!
-我只希望他还没有走 -等一下，让我看看
Andy's still packing. But he's almost done!
安弟还在打包，不过就快好了
-He lives halfway across town. -We'll never get there in time!
-他住的地方很不耶 -我们绝对来不及赶到
-Come on, Buster. -Is that it, honey? You got everything?
-通来，自小子，遇来 -都收拾好了吐?
Yeah. Just a few more boxes - In my room.
只剩下羽间的禾个箱子
Okay. Come on.
来吧
That's enough. That's enough. That's enough!
角了 !
All right. Go. Go, go!
好吧，快走
Okay. All clear.
好，安全
There you are.
找到了
-There you go. -Buzz.
-进去吧 一巴斯
-This isn't goodbye. -Hey, Woody. Have fun at college.
-这不是永别 -胡迪，到大学要好好玩
Yeah, but not too much fun.
对啊，不过别玩过头
-Woody, take care of Andy. -Yeah.
-胡迪，要好好恩疗安弟 -没错
He's a good kid. Tell him to get a haircut.
他是个好孩子，叫他苋头桶
Sure thing.
没问题
Jessie, you'll be okay in the attic?
翌尹，在阅楼没问题吧 ?
‘Course I will. Besides, 1 know about
当然啦 我能把巴斯调成
-Buzz's Spanish mode. -My what?
一西班牙文模式 -我的什么 ?
Honey, you want some food for the road?
甜心，要带东西在路上吃吗?
I'll get something on the way.
“阅楼”
You know where to find us, cowboy.
你知道我们在哪里，牛仔
Did you say goodbye to Molly?
你跟茉莉说再见了吐?
Mom, we've said goodbye like 10 times.
妈，我们说了不只十炎了
Andy.
噢，安生
Mon, it's okay.
妈，列担心
I know. It's just...
我知道，只是…
I wish I could always be with you.
真希望可以永速联在你身尊
You will be, Mom.
会的，怒
Hey, aren't you gonna say goodbye to Buster?
你不四臭小子说再见吗 ?
Of course I am. Who's a good doggy?
当然要啦，谁是乎猩狗 ?
Who's a good doggy? I'm gonna miss you. I'm gonna miss you.
我会想你的 我也会很想你
-I'm gonna miss you. -Don't, Andy.
安弟，列人这样
Good boy. He's telling you to go already.
乖狗狗 他说你该出发了
Come on. Get the rest of your things.
去拿你的东西
Okay, Buster. Now don't let Molly near my stuff.
臭小子，别让茉莉碰我的东西
Hey, Mom! So, you really think I should donate these?
妈 ! 人真的要我把它们捐出去吗 ?
It's up to you, honey. Whatever you wanna do.
你决定，你要怎广做都行
“Don't go in there! The bakery is haunted!"
别进去 ! 蛋糙让有鬼 !
“Are you crazy? You'll wake up all the ghosts.”
你疯啦 ? 你会把鬼都吵醒
“Look out! The ghosts are throwing pies!"
小心!鬼在丢派了 !
Mom.
杂
-Andy? -Hi.
-安弟 ? -嗨
Wow. Look at you.
看看你
Well, I hear you're off to college.
职说你要去上大学了
Yeah. Right now, actually.
对啊，现在就要走了
So, what can we do for you?
我们能者你什么忙 ?
I have some toys here.
我有一些玩具
You hear that, Bonnie?
职到了吗，孝妮?
So, you're Bonnie?
原来你就是邦刀
I'm Andy.
我是安弟
Someone told me you're really good with toys.
有人说你对玩具非常好
These are mine, but I'm going away now,
这些是我的，但我要元并家
so 1 need someone really special to play with them.
需要一个很特列的人跟他们玩
This is Jessie, the roughest, toughest cowgirl in the whole West.
这是浴缘，西部最强悍的女牛仔
She loves critters, but none more than her best pal, Bullseye.
她喜数动物 但她最属地最好的采伴红心
Here.
拿去
This is Rex, the meanest, most terrifying dinosaur who ever lived!
这是抱抱龙 拖是史上最多狠最可怕的恐龙
The Potato Heads. Mr. and Mrs. You gotta keep 'em together,
这是蛋头先生和和蛋头太太 列拆散人他们
‘cause they're madly in love.
因为他们深爱对方
Now Slinky here is as loyal as any dog you could want.
弹筑狗跟所有狗一样患心耿了
And Hamm, he'll keep your money safe,
至认火腿，他会看好你的仅
but he’s also one of the most dastardly villains of all time, evil Dr. Pork Chop.
但他也是有史以来最壤的大玉蛋 那恶猪排博士
These little dudes are from a strange alien world.
这些小停伙来自奇怪的星球
Pizza Planet.
比荐星球
And this
还有这个…
is Buzz Lightyear, the coolest toy ever!
他是巴斯光年，最酷的玩具
Look, he can fly and shoot lasers!
看，他能屎，还能发射雷射光
He's sworn to protect the galaxy from the evil Emperor Zurg.
他发拆要打败收恶皇帝札克
To infinity and beyond!
飞向宇密…浩瀚扰地 !
Now, you gotta promise to take good care of these guys.
我要你答应会好好照顾这些信人炙
They mean a lot to me.
他们…对我意义重大
My cowboy!
我的牛仔 !
Woody? What's he doing in there?
胡迪?他怎庆会在这壬?
-"There's a snake in my boot." -Wha...?
我的就子里有蛇
Now, Woody, he's been my pal for as long as I can remember.
从我有记改以来 胡迪就是我的好彩伴
He's brave, like a cowboy should be.
他就像牛仔一样勇敢
And kind. And smart.
善良隐明
But the thing that makes Woody special is he'll never give up on you.
不遇胡迪会这广特别 是因鸭他永下不会放率你
Ever.
永速不会
He'll be there for you, no matter what.
把论如何，他都是你的支柱
You think you can take care of him for me?
你能帮我照顾他吐?
Okay then.
好吧
Oh, no! Dr. Pork Chop's attacking the haunted bakery!
不 ! 猪排博士攻贡于鬼蛋糕让 !
The ghosts are getting away. Woody'll stop ‘em!
和鬼要逃走了，胡迪会拉住他们
Buzz Lightyear to the rescue!
巴斯光年拯救字宙 !
And we'll actually need the rocket.
我们还需要火稍
They're getting away! Come on, Bullseye!
他们要逃了 ! 快点 ! 红心
We need to get in the spaceship. The volcano is gonna erupt.
我们得回到太空船上 火山快要爆发了
Look! They're being attacked by a real dog!
他们被真正的狗攻击 了
You can eat my poisonous scones!
你们可以吃我的毒里饼
Mr. and Mrs. Potato Head are in trouble.
蛋头夫妇有危险了 !
Get on, Woody.
来吧，胡这
It's my friend Woody.
是我的朋友，胡迪
Buzz, hurry! Get your extra turbo booster.
巴斯快点 ! 带上你的渴输推进器
Thanks, guys.
谢了，大彩儿
Look, Mommy. They're all playing together.
看，妈味，他们玩在一起了
Come on. Let's get some lunch.
快点，进来吃午人饭了
So long, partner.
再见了，彩伴
Hey, Buzz. You haven't met Bonnie's toys yet. Hey, come here.
巴斯，你还没见遇邦妮的玩具 遇来
You're gonna love them. Buzz, this is Dolly.
你一定会喜欢他们 巴斯，这是桃莉
New toys!
新玩具 !
Noses.
鼻子
“So Il guess you could say Sunnyside is sunny once again!
我猜阳光托儿又充满了阳光
“Hope to hear from you soon. We're all super excited about your new home.
希望能早点收到回信 你们找到新家我们都好机硅
“Hugs and kisses to everyone."
爱你们唾
That Barbie has some nice handwriting.
芭比的字体还真漂亮
Buzz, Barbie didn't write this.
这封信不是芭比写的
-Grab the sword! -I got it!
-拿那把剑 -拿到了
-Okay, go for the... -Triple bonus!
-快去拿… -三倍奖金 !
-Watch out! -We got the cloak of darkness!
一小心 上 -我们有黑暗斗丰 !
-Run, run! -My arms are never long enough!
-快跑 ! -我的手展永速不金长 !
I'll do it! This is it! This is it!
让我来 ! 趁现在 !
-Yes! -We did it!
-耶 ! 一成功了 !
High-five! Hold on.
出掌 ! 等一等
Well, it's official. You guys made the wall.
蕉喜啦，你们都在糙上了
-Look at this! -Golly bob howdy! That's me!
一你看看 -我的天 !那是我耶!
We're all up here! Hey, Chuckles, lookin’ good.
我们全在上面! 恰克，你还不加嘛!
Yeah, she really got your smile.
她把你的笑容书得不错
I told you kids! Stay out of my butt!
我说晨了，郊我尼股速一点
But soft, what light through yonder window breaks?
窗口延进什么秒美的光亮?
Romeo, o Romeo, wherefore art thou Romeo?
嗓，稚密欧，如密欧 和为什么你是中密欧 ?
Next season, we're doing Cats.
下一季我们要演《猎》
Or might I suggest Hamlet?
我能建议演《哈姆雷特》吗 ?
Yeah. Detached wing. Cosmetic damage.
可拆务翅膀，外表受损
Nothing a little duct tape can't fix.
只要贴一点肋带就能修好
I don't know what came over me.
我不知道我是怎床了
Just go with it, Buzz.
你跟著跳就对了，巴斯